<resources>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1857181957836361</string>
    <string name="app_name">TripSplit</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to TripSplit, where you can share Journeys and connect with new friends</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="last_message">Messages</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="date_text">Mon 16,June 16</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="spinner_title_sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="about_me_heading">About Me</string>
    <string name="review_text">Reviews</string>
    <string name="source_dest_text">Dubai To Zanzibar</string>
    <string name="about_me_txt">Sed us perspicatis unde omnis iste natus error sit valuptatem accusantium doloremque laudantium, totam rem aperiam, eaque ipsa quae ab voluptatem accusantium doloremque laudantium,\n tatam rem aperiam</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="white_chat_box_text">Sed ut per hgfrehb wehry fwegfrwh hjgfd ugwebhjg ghdtg wygejwh vhgf tweugbn </string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="shareit">Share it</string>
    <string name="editpic">Pick Image</string>
    <string name="pick_from_galary">Pick from gallery</string>
    <string name="take_picture">Take picture</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_account_register_here"><u>Don\'t have account? Register here!</u></string>
    <string name="editaddress">Address</string>
    <string name="editcountry">Country</string>
    <string name="url">http://netforce.biz/tripesplit/mobileApp/api/</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog">Please wait</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait for a moment</string>
    <string name="appkey">abcd</string>
    <string name="forgot_password"><u>Forgot password?</u></string>
    <string name="choose_weather">Choose whether you
would like to Post a Trip
or Search Splitz….
</string>
    <string name="connect_with_fb">Connect with <b>Facebook</b></string>
    <string name="third_tutorial">Got space to split? Want to find someone to take a trip with?</string>
    <string name="second_tutorial">Meet in a public place try to choose mixed groups don\'t give away too much personal info when</string>
    <string name="first_tutorial">Sign up and be apart of the next big thing in Social Travel</string>
    <string name="fourth_tutorial">Save your hard earned cash. Split your cost with new travel buddies.</string>
    <string name="editdob">Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="departure_address">Departure Address</string>
    <string name="destination_address">Destination Address</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="select_date_and_time">Select Date and Time</string>
    <string name="total_cost">Total Cost</string>
    <string name="currency_not_found">Currency not found</string>
    <string name="return_etd">Return ETD</string>
    <string name="return_eta">Return ETA</string>
    <string name="passenger">Passenger</string>
    <string name="vehicle_type">Vehicle Type</string>
    <string name="selected_place">Selected Place</string>
    <string name="choose_source">Choose Source</string>
    <string name="choose_destination">Choose Destination</string>
    <string name="itinerary">Itinerary</string>
    <string name="add_image">Add Image</string>
    <string name="postdetail">Trip created successfully</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="destination">Destination</string>
    <string name="source">Source</string>
    <string name="best_match">Best match</string>
    <string name="low_cost">Lowest Cost</string>
    <string name="highest_cost">Highest Cost</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="cantbeempy">Field cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="no_split_found">No split found</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="search_group">Search Group</string>
    <string name="choose_category">Choose Category</string>
    <string name="create_group">Create Group</string>
    <string name="group_title">Group Title</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="invite_friend">Invite Friends</string>
    <string name="search_spliz">Search Splitz</string>
    <string name="post_trip">Post Trip</string>
    <string name="my_splitz">My Splitz</string>
    <string name="my_trip">My Tripz</string>
    <string name="messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="dummy">dummy</string>
    <string name="lorem_description">"There is no one who loves pain itself, who seeks after it and wants to have it, simply because it is pain..."</string>
    <string name="group">Group</string>
    <string name="how_it_works">How it works</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="age_group">Age group</string>
    <string name="travelling_with">Travelling With</string>
    <string name="action_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="removegroup">Leave Group</string>
    <string name="leavegroup">Are you sure you want to leave the group?</string>
    <string name="not_in_group">You are not in the group!</string>
    <string name="about_me">About me</string>
    <string name="aeroplane_splitz">Aeroplane Splitz</string>
    <string name="car_splitz">Car Splitz</string>
    <string name="bus_splitz">Bus Splitz</string>
    <string name="boat_splitz">Boat Splitz</string>
    <string name="globe">Globe</string>
    <string name="list">List</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="deleteconversation">Delete Conversation</string>
    <string name="deletechat">Are you sure you want to delete the conversation?</string>

<string name="privacy_policy">"PRIVACY AND DATA PROTECTION POLICY

1. General

1.1. Tripsplitz Ltd (“we” or “us”) take the privacy of your personal information very seriously. Our Privacy Policy is lays out our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide via the www.Tripsplitz.com website and other associated partner websites, mobile applications, microsites and sub-sites (the “Site”).

1.2. By using this Site or any services we offer, you are consenting to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information about you in accordance with, and are agreeing to be bound by, this Privacy Policy.

1.3. Tripsplitz Ltd adheres and conforms to the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA) and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 (SI 2003/2426) (2003 Privacy Regulations) as revised by the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) (Amendment) Regulations 2011 (SI 2011/1208) (together, Revised 2003 Privacy Regulations). These Regulations implemented Directive 2002/58/EC concerning the processing of personal data and the protection of privacy in the electronic communications sector (E-Privacy Directive).

2. Ways that we collect information

2.1. We may collect and process the following information or data (including personal information and information that can be uniquely identified with you) about you:

2.1.1. Passport, driving license and such other documents and information that may be required from time to time including your name, address including postcodes), date of birth and if you are a Trip Sharer certain information about your Vehicle to register with the Site or to access other services provided by us;

2.1.2. Your e-mail address and a password;

2.1.3. A mobile phone number;

2.1.4. A record of any correspondence between you and us;

2.1.5. A record of any bookings you have made or advertisements you have placed with or through the Site;

2.1.6. Your replies to any surveys or questionnaires that we may use for research purposes;

2.1.7. Details of accounting or financial transactions including transactions carried out through the Site or otherwise. This may include information such as details of Trips (as described in our Conditions) you have booked or offered through the Site;

2.1.8. Details of your visits to the Site and the resources that you access;

2.1.9. Information we may require from you when you report a problem with the Site.

2.1.10. Information about you which we may receive from other sources.

2.2. We only collect such information when you choose to supply it to us. You do not have to supply any personal information to us, but you may not be able to take advantage of all the services we offer without doing so.

2.3. Information is also gathered without you actively providing it, through the use of various technologies and methods such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and cookies. These methods do not collect or store personal information.

2.4. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), so you can access the Internet. It is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information, because in most cases an IP address can only be traced back to your ISP or the large company or organisation that provides your internet access (such as your employer if you are at work).

2.5. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, and determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to our site, and to administer and improve the site.

3. Cookies

3.1. A cookie is a piece of data stored locally on your computer and contains information about your activities on the Internet. The information in a cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information you submit to our site.

3.2. On the Site, we use cookies to track users’ progress through the Site, allowing us to make improvements based on usage data. We also use cookies if you log in to one of our online services to enable you to remain logged in to that service. A cookie helps you get the best out of the Site and helps us to provide you with a more customised service.

3.3. Once you close your browser, our access to the cookie terminates. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. To change your browser settings, you should go to your advanced preferences.

3.4. We have a clear cookies notice on the home page of the website. If you continue to use the Site having seen the notice, then we assume you are happy for us to use the cookies described above.

3.5. If you choose not to accept the cookies, this will not affect your access to the majority of information available on the Site. However, you will not be able to make full use of our online services.

4. Use

4.1. We may use this information to:

4.1.1. ensure that the content of the Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer and customise the Site to your preferences;

4.1.2. assist in making general improvements to the Site;

4.1.3. carry out and administer any obligations arising from any agreements entered into between you and us;

4.1.4. allow you to participate in features of the Site and other services;

4.1.5. contact you and notify you about changes to the Site or the services we offer (except where you have asked us not to do this);

4.1.6. analyse how users are making use of the Site and for internal marketing and research purposes.

4.1.7 Ensure that you comply with the Conditions and applicable law.

5. Sharing your information

5.1.1. As part of our booking process and in order to provide our services information may be passed to a Trip Splitter (if you are a Trip Sharer) or to a Trip Sharer (if you are a Trip Splitter).

5.1.2. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation (for example, if required to do so by a court order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime or upon requisition made by government agencies);

5.1.3. in order to enforce any terms of use that apply to any of the Site, or to enforce any other terms and conditions or agreements for our Services that may apply;

5.1.4. we may share information with our international partner websites where you have made a booking through the Site with a user of our partner websites or where you have used the Site to interact with a third party;

5.1.5. we may transfer your personal information to a third party as part of a sale of some or all of our business and assets to any third party or as part of any business restructuring or reorganisation, but we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected;

5.1.6. to protect the rights, property, or safety of Tripsplitz Ltd, the Site’s users, or any other third parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

5.1.7 for the purpose of verification by third party service providers of the information contained in the IDs and other documents that may be collected from the Members at the time of registration or at any other time during their use of the Site as may be required. Third party service providers will process data under Tripsplitz’s control and will be bound by the same degree of security and care as Tripsplitz’s under this Privacy and Data Protection Policy.

Notwithstanding anything contained herein or the terms &amp; conditions, Tripsplitz hereby disclaims any liability arising from the verification of the IDs and other documents by third party service providers including but not limited to its accuracy, reliability, and originality;

5.1.8 for the purpose of maintaining internal quality, training and updating the customers about the Services of Tripsplitz.

5.2. Tripsplitz may moderate the messages you exchange on the Site. Tripsplitz will not sell, transfer, distribute, disclose your communications to any third party without your consent, unless such disclosure is mandated under applicable laws.

5.3. Other than as set out above, we shall not disclose any of your personal information, but may use your trip data for the benefit of the company.

6. Access to and correction of personal information

6.1. We will take all reasonable steps in accordance with our legal obligations to update or correct personally identifiable information in our possession that you submit via this Site.

6.2. The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £50.00 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. If you wish to see details of any personal information that we hold about you, please contact us by way of our support page.

6.3. We take all appropriate steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our Site and to protect such information for loss, misuse, and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We use leading technologies and encryption software to safeguard your data, and operate strict security standards to prevent any unauthorised access to it.

6.4. Where you use passwords, usernames, or other special access features on this site, you also have a responsibility to take reasonable steps to safeguard them.

7. Other websites or Applications

7.1. This Site contains links and references to other websites and applications, by way of adverts and integrated links. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites.

7.2. We cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies and practices of sites that are not operated by us, even if you access them via the Site. We advise that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.

7.3. In addition, if you came to this Site via a third-party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners or operators of that third-party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third-party site and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.

8. Transferring your information outside of Great Britain

8.1. As part of the services offered to you through the Site, the information you provide to us may originate, be transferred to, and stored in, countries outside of Great Britain. By way of example, this may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located in a country outside of Great Britain or one of our members or service providers is located in a country outside of Great Britain. We may also share information with other equivalent national bodies, which may be located in countries worldwide. The information provided by you may be transferred to a third party if it is necessary for the performance of any contract between us and the said third party or upon receipt of your consent to data transfer. If we transfer your information outside of Great Britain in this way, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this privacy policy and in accordance with applicable laws including but not limited to Information Technology Act, 2000 and the rules framed thereunder.

8.2. If you use the Site while you are outside Great Britain, your information may be stored and transferred outside Great Britain in order to provide you with those services.

8.3. By submitting your personal information to us you agree to the transfer, storing or processing of your information outside Great Britain in the manner described above.

9. Notification of changes to our Privacy Policy

We will post details of any changes to our Privacy Policy on the Site to help ensure you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and in what circumstances, if any, we share it with other parties.

10. Contact us

If at any time you would like to contact us with your views about our privacy practices, or with any enquiry relating to your personal information, you can do so by way of our contact page or our support page.

Should you wish to no longer receive our Tripsplitz Newz (marketing newsletters), you may click on the unsubscribe link located within each email and/or manage your preferences directly in the page notification of your dashboard."

</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition">"Tripsplitz Terms


1. GENERAL CONDITION OF USE

1.1 Scope and Definitions

These General Conditions of Use apply to all services provided by Tripsplitz (defined herein below). Tripsplitz owns and operates the Site (defined herein below) in Great Britain.

Defined Terms

“Tripsplitz” means Tripsplitz Ltd, registered in Scotland under company number SC553878, and hereafter referred to as Tripsplitz. The registered office of Tripsplitz is at 2/5 Mulberry Place, Edinburgh, EH6 4BT, Great Britain.

“Trip Sharing” means the sharing of a Vehicle for a Trip by a Trip Sharer carrying a Trip Splitter for that Trip in exchange for a Cost Contribution;

“Conditions” mean these General Conditions of Use, including the Good Conduct Charter and Privacy Policy of Tripsplitz as notified on the Site. https://www.Tripsplitz.com/Triplife/

“Cost Contribution” means the amount agreed between the Trip Sharer and the Trip Splitter in relation to the Trip which is payable by the Trip Splitter as their contribution towards the costs of the Trip.

“Trip Splitter” or “Passenger” means a Member who has accepted an offer to be transported by a Trip Sharer and includes all other persons who accompany such Member in the Vehicle for the Trip.

“Trip Sharer” means a Member who through the Site offers to share a journey with a Trip Splitter in exchange for the Cost Contribution.

“Member” refers to a registered user of the Site.

“Service” refers to any service provided by Tripsplitz through the Site to any Member.

“Site” means www.tripsplitz.com, www.tripsplitz.co.uk, www.tripsplitz.net, www. tripsplitz.org and any other website or mobile application maintained or operated by Tripsplitz which offers similar services including any microsites or sub-sites.

“Trip” means a given journey in relation to which a Trip Sharer and a Trip Splitter have agreed upon a transaction through the Site.

“User Account” means an account with the Site opened by a Member and used in order to access the Service provided by Tripsplitz through the Site.

“Vehicle” means the vehicle offered by a Trip Sharer for Trip Sharing, whether it is automotive, plane or boat.

1.2 Acceptance of Conditions

The Conditions apply to any and all use of the Site by a Member. By using the Site, the Members signify their acceptance to these Conditions in full and agree to be bound by them.

No access to the Services will be permitted unless the Conditions are accepted in full. No Member is entitled to accept part only of the Conditions. If a Member does not agree to the Conditions, such Member may not use the Services.

All Members agree to comply with the Conditions and accept that their personal data may be processed in accordance with the Privacy Policy.

In the event that any Member fails to comply with any of the Conditions, Tripsplitz reserves the right, but not the obligation at its own discretion, to withdraw the User Account in question and suspend or withdraw all Services to that Member without notice.

These Conditions are intended to create binding rights and obligations between Members and Tripsplitz in accordance with the Great Britainn Contract Act, 1976.

1.3 Variation of the Conditions, Site and Service

Tripsplitz reserves the right to modify the Conditions at any time. In addition, Tripsplitz may vary or amend the Services provided through the Site, the Site functionality and/ or the “look and feel” of the Site at any time without notice and without liability to Members.

Any modification to the Site, Services or Conditions will take effect as soon as such changes are published on the Site, subject to communication of any material change to the Conditions to the Members in an e-mail.

Members will be deemed to have accepted any varied Conditions in the event that they use any Services offered through the Site following publication of the varied Conditions. Changes will not apply to any bookings which have been made prior to publication of the varied Conditions.

2. GENERAL TERMS

2.1 Relationship

No arrangement between the Members and Tripsplitz shall constitute or be deemed to constitute an agency, partnership, joint venture or the like between the Members and Tripsplitz.

2.2 Suspension or Withdrawal of Site Access

In the event of non-compliance on your part with all or some of the Conditions, you acknowledge and accept that Tripsplitz can at any time, without prior notification, interrupt or suspend, temporarily or permanently, all or part of the service or your access to the Site (including in particular your User Account).

2.3 Intellectual Property

The format and content included on the Site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data compilations, and software, is the property of Tripsplitz, its affiliates or its content suppliers and is protected by Great Britain and international copyright, authors’ rights and database right laws.

All rights are reserved in relation to any registered and unregistered trademarks (whether owned or licensed to Tripsplitz) which appear on the Site.

The Site or any portion of the Site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without the express written consent of Tripsplitz. No person is entitled to systematically extract and/or re-utilise parts of the contents of the Site or mobile application without the express written consent of Tripsplitz. In particular, the use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools to extract (whether once or many times) for re-utilisation of any substantial parts of this Site is strictly prohibited.

2.4 Content of the Site Provided by the Members

By displaying content on this Site, Members expressly grant a license to Tripsplitz to display the content and to use it for any of our other business purposes.

Members of this Site are expressly asked not to publish any defamatory, misleading or offensive content or any content which infringes any other person’s intellectual property rights (e.g. copyright). Any such content which is contrary to Tripsplitz’s policy and Tripsplitz does not accept liability in respect of such content, and the Member responsible will be personally liable for any damages or other liability arising and agrees to indemnify Tripsplitz in relation to any liability it may suffer as a result of any such content. However as soon as Tripsplitz becomes aware of infringing content, Tripsplitz shall do everything it can to remove such content from the Site as soon as possible.

2.5 Partner Sites

Tripsplitz reserves the right to reproduce any information that appears on the Site or on the partner sites.

In particular, ads published on one of the sites maintained or co-maintained by Tripsplitz may be reproduced on other sites maintained or co-maintained by Tripsplitz or third parties.

3. USE OF THE SERVICE

3.1 User Account and Accuracy of Information

In order to use the Services each Member must create a User Account and agrees to provide any personal information requested by Tripsplitz. In particular, Members will be required to provide their first name, last name, age, title, valid telephone number and email address. Use of the Site is limited to those over the age of 17 years at the time of registration.

Members agree and accept that all of the information they provide to Tripsplitz when setting up their User Account and at any other time shall be true, correct, complete and accurate in all respects. Members also agree that any information supplied to Tripsplitz or posted on the Site in connection with any Trip, Vehicle or Trip Sharing will be true, accurate and complete.

Members agree and understand that Tripsplitz does not undertake any verification to confirm the accuracy of any information provided by the Members on the Site or to a Trip Sharer or Trip Splitter, as the case maybe. Tripsplitz will not be liable to any Member in the event that any information provided by another Member is false, incomplete, inaccurate, misleading or fraudulent.

Unless expressly agreed by Tripsplitz, Members are limited to one User Account per Member. No User Account may be created on behalf of or in order to impersonate another person.

3.2 No Commercial Activity and Status of Tripsplitz

The Site and the Services are strictly limited to providing a Service for Trip Sharers and Trip Splitters to trip share in a private capacity. The Services may not be used to offer or accept Trip Sharing for hire or reward or for profit or in any commercial or professional context. The Services may be used only to offer or accept Trip Sharing in exchange for sharing the cost of the Trip between the Trip Sharer and the Trip Splitter.

Trip Sharers agree not to obtain any hire or reward or make profit in any form, from any Trip. The Service and the Cost Contribution may only be used to discharge the Trip Sharer’s costs and may not be used to generate any hiring charges or reward or profit in any form for the Trip Sharer. The Trip Sharer is not entitled to make profit by virtue of the amount of the Cost Contribution, the types of Trips offered by a Trip Sharer, the frequency of such Trips or the number of Trip Splitters transported. This applies to all activities, arrangements and Services booked using the Site and any additional services or activities which may be agreed between Trip Sharer and Trip Splitter through the Site.

The Trip Sharer must not provide any additional services to the Trip Splitter in exchange for hiring charges or any reward or for profit or otherwise (and the Trip Splitter may not accept or ask for any such services) including (without limitation) package delivery, waiting time, additional drop offs and pick-ups and collecting additional passengers (other than the Trip Splitter).

All Trips, collection points and destinations must be pre-agreed through the Site between the Trip Sharer and Trip Splitter. Trip Sharers may not collect any Trip Splitters from any location which has not been pre-agreed with all Trip Splitters through the Site.

Members are reminded that using the Services and offering Trips for hire or reward or in a commercial or professional capacity may invalidate a Trip Sharer’s insurance and invite adverse legal actions by the road transport authorities. Tripsplitz shall not be in for any loss or damage incurred by a Member as a result of any or breach by a Member of these Conditions including where any Trip Sharer (in breach of these terms) offers Services through the Site in a professional or commercial capacity (thereby potentially invalidating their insurance) and breach of any agreement between the Trip Sharer and the Trip Splitter. Any offering of Trips in violation of the Conditions shall be at the sole risk such Member and Tripsplitz shall have no liability towards Members for such violations.

Status of Tripsplitz

Neither Tripsplitz nor the Site provides any transport services. The Site is a communications platform for Members to transact with one another. Tripsplitz does not interfere with Trips, destinations or timings. The agreement for Trip Sharing is between the Trip Sharer and the Trip Splitter. Tripsplitz is not a party to any agreement or transaction between Members, nor is Tripsplitz liable in respect of any matter arising which relates to a booking between Members. Tripsplitz is not and will not act as an agent for any Member.

Any breach of these Conditions will give rise to immediate suspension of such Member’s User Account and they may be restricted from accessing any further Services.

3.3 Trip Sharer and Trip Splitter Obligations

Trip Sharer’s obligations

The Trip Sharer agrees:

That the Trip shall not be for any fraudulent, unlawful or criminal activity.

That they will ensure for the Vehicle, a comprehensive insurance policy, which provides insurance cover to the occupants in the Vehicle and covers third party liability.

That they will present themselves on time and at the place agreed with the specified Vehicle;

That they will immediately inform all Trip Splitters of any change whatsoever to the Trip. If one or more Trip Splitters have made a booking and the Trip Sharer decides to change any aspect of the Trip, the Trip Sharer undertakes to contact all Trip Splitters who have made a booking in relation to that Trip and to obtain the agreement of all Trip Splitters to the change. If a Trip Splitter refuses the change, they are entitled to a full refund and without any compensation being paid to the Trip Sharer.

The Trip Sharer must comply with the Good Conduct Charter at all times.

The Trip Sharer must wait for the Trip Splitter at the pickup point for at least 30 minutes after the agreed time (however, the Trip Splitter is expected to be punctual).

Trip Splitter obligations

The Trip Splitter agrees:

That the Trip shall not be for any fraudulent, unlawful or criminal activity.

That they will present themselves on time and at the place agreed with the Trip Sharer;

That they will immediately inform the Trip Sharer or Tripsplitz if they are required to cancel a Trip.

That they will comply with the Good Conduct Charter at all times.

The Trip Splitter agrees to wait at the pickup point for at least 30 minutes after the agreed time for the Trip Sharer to arrive.

That they will pay the Cost Contribution to the Trip Sharer.

If the Trip Splitter or Trip Sharer fail to comply with any of these terms or any other Conditions Tripsplitz reserves the right to keep information relating to the breach, to publish or disclose this information on the Member’s online profile and to suspend or withdraw the Member’s access to the Site.

That they shall ensure that all other persons who accompany the Trip Splitter in the Trip comply with these Conditions as applicable to a Trip Splitter.

3.4 Insurance

The Trip Sharer agrees to ensure a comprehensive insurance to cover third party liability, the occupants of the Vehicle and the Trip offered or booked through the Site. The Trip Sharer agrees that they will, on request, provide the Trip Splitter with evidence, in advance of the Trip, of the complete validity of the insurance policy. All Car Shares also undertake to hold a valid driving licence and that the Trip Sharer will own or will be entitled to use the Vehicle and that the Vehicle will have a valid qualification with local law that the vehicle is roadworthy. The Trip Splitter is entitled to request evidence of the Trip Sharer’s insurance, registration certificate (‘log book’), driving licence, taxation if required by local law and proof of road worthiness .

It is Tripsplitz’s understanding that governmental authorities take the view that a Trip Splitter who contributes only towards travel expenses is treated as travelling without hire or reward to the driver, and is therefore a third party passenger who is covered by comprehensive third party insurance policy in Great Britain. However Tripsplitz gives no warranty or assurance in this regard and it is the Trip Sharer’s responsibility to verify that their insurance provides adequate cover.

It is up to each Trip Sharer and Trip Splitter to confirm with each other that the vehicle operator is covered by valid insurance. The Trip Sharer must confirm that the insurance policy allows them to carry Trip Splitters and that the insurance policy covers all Trip Splitters and any accident or incident which may occur during a Trip.

The Trip Sharer and the Trip Splitter are aware that standard non-commercial insurance policies may refuse to cover loss or damage arising in the event that the Trip Sharer had made or was seeking to make a profit.

The Trip Sharer may collect no payment from the Trip Splitter other than the Cost Contribution and the Trip Sharer must not in any event provide Vehicle on hire or for reward in any form.

The Trip Sharer therefore undertakes to calculate their expenses (fuel, toll, maintenance, repairs, depreciation and insurance of their vehicle) and guarantees that the total Cost Contributions requested from their Trip Splitters does not result in the Vehicle running for hire or for reward for the Trip Sharer.

If the Trip Sharer does receive any hiring charges or reward, or if the insurers repudiate or refuse to accept any claim arising during a Trip for any other reason, the Trip Sharer will be responsible for the financial consequences, losses and damages arising and Tripsplitz will not be liable under any circumstances to the Trip Sharer or the Trip Splitter.

Tripsplitz reserves the right, but not the obligation at its own discretion, to suspend immediately the account of a user including the money displayed and to make aware to competent authorities any professional activity.

3.5 Management of Disputes Between Members

Tripsplitz may at its sole discretion provide its Members with an online service for resolving disputes. This service is non-binding. Tripsplitz is under no obligation to seek to resolve disputes and this service is offered at Tripsplitz’s sole discretion and may be withdrawn at any time.
2.7 Verification of IDs and Phone number

By accepting the terms and conditions contained herein, every Member or any person who wishes to register as a Member hereby agrees and consents to the fact that Tripsplitz may collect IDs / documents belonging to them including, but not limited to passport, driving license for the purpose of verification of the information contained in such IDs / documents by third party service providers.

In order to increase trustworthiness, prevent typos and wrong numbers, Member may verify their mobile number. The Member may do this by providing Tripsplitz with their mobile phone number, after which the Member will receive a SMS with a 4-digit code which can be validated on the Site. This service is free of charge, except for the possible cost levied by a Member’s mobile phone operator for receiving the SMS.

3.6 International Trips and International Bookings

Bookings may be made through the Site for international Trips. An International Trip means any Trip which includes any travel outside of Great Britain. If a booking is made for an International Trip, Trip Sharers must ensure that their insurance covers travel for the country where the trip is shared. The Trip Sharer must also ensure that their vehicle is compliant with all relevant rules and restrictions applicable in this country.

3.7 Types of Booking and Payment

3.7.1 Tripsplitz offers to its Members an online booking service (hereinafter, the “Booking Service”) with a view to facilitate the booking of seats by Passengers.

Tripsplitz reserves the right not to offer the Booking Service to a Trip due to: (i) changes to applicable law, changes in the practice of regulatory authorities or changes in case law, (ii) changes to market practices or technology changes, (iii) changes of business considerations underlying the Booking Services, and (iv) other important and valid reasons

Tripsplitz reserves the right to limit the number and/or class of Members eligible to the Booking Service for any Trip.

3.7.2 How to book a Split for a Trip: The Trip Sharer provides details of his or her Trip on the Site, specifying date and time for departure and destination points, the amount of the Cost Contribution per seat and all other relevant travel conditions.

The Passenger books one or more seats in the vehicle for that Trip from the Site exclusively by clicking on the button « Book » (hereinafter, the “Booking”).

Tripsplitz will then send an email confirmation to each of the Trip Sharer and the Trip Splitters confirming the Booking (hereinafter, the “Booking Confirmation”). Once a Booking Confirmation has been sent, the Booking is complete and a separate binding agreement for Trip Sharing relating to theTrip shall be formed between the Trip Sharer and Trip Splitter.

Members accept that given the nature of the service Trip Sharers and Trip Splitters will have no recourse to Tripsplitz for any aspect of the transaction including in relation to cancellation, last minute changes, failure by the Trip Sharer or the Trip Splitter to turn up or non-payment of the Cost Contribution. In particular, it is the Trip Sharer’s responsibility to collect payment from the Trip Splitter at the time of the Trip.

Tripsplitz will not contact either party and will take no other steps whatsoever than those described above to manage the booking. The operation of the Trip is solely managed by the respective Trip Sharer and Trip Splitter(s).

Please note that Tripsplitz reserves the right to change any aspect of the Site or the Service which may include adding new services (which may require payment) or withdrawing any existing Services. Tripsplitz does not guarantee that the Site will be functional at all times and Services may be suspended during such period when the Site is not in operation. Tripsplitz will not be liable to any of the Members in case where the Site or localised servers are non-operational.

3.8 Messages between Members

Tripsplitz may review, scan, and moderate the messages the Members exchange with each other through the Site in particular for fraud prevention, customer support purposes, enforcement of the contracts entered into with Tripsplitz’s members (such as the Conditions) and ensure compliance with applicable law. For example, in order to prevent the circumventing of its Booking Service, Tripsplitz may scan and analyse messages sent through the platform to check that they do not include any contact details or references to any other website.

By using the Site and accepting the T&amp;C’s, the Member agrees that Tripsplitz, in its sole discretion, may review, analyse and moderate the messages exchanged through the Site.

By using the messaging or group chat features of the Site, the Member undertakes not to write and/or send any message prohibited by applicable law. In particular, the Member undertakes to refrain from writing/sending any message which content:

belongs to another person and to which the Member does not have any right to;
is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous defamatory, obscene, pornographic ;
harms minors in any way;
infringes any patent, trademark, copyright or other proprietary rights;
violates any law for the time being in force;
deceives or misleads the addressee about the origin of such messages or communicates any information which is grossly offensive or menacing in nature;
impersonates another person;
contains software viruses that limit the functionality of any computer resource; and
threatens the unity, integrity, defense, security or sovereignty of Great Britain, friendly relations with foreign states, or public order or causes incitement to the commission of any cognizable offence or prevents investigation of any offence or is insulting any other nation.

Tripsplitz reserves the right to filter or delete the messages and suspend or terminate the User Account of the Member and the access of the Member to the Site if it appears during the moderation of the messages or chats sent by the Member that s/he does not comply with the Conditions and/or applicable law.

3.9 Contacting Members

 By accepting the terms and conditions contained herein, every Member hereby agrees and gives consent to Tripsplitz to communicate via phone calls, sms, email and such other means as Tripsplitz may deem fit. Such communications to Members may be recorded through technical support provided by third parties for the purpose of training, quality and for regularly updating the Members about the services of Tripsplitz.

4. DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY

4.1 Members may access the Services on the Site at their own risk and using their best and prudent judgment before entering into any arrangements with other Members through the Site. Tripsplitz will neither be liable nor responsible for any actions or inactions of Members nor any breach of conditions, representations or warranties by the Members. Tripsplitz hereby expressly disclaims and any and all responsibility and liability in arising out of the use of the Site.

4.2 Tripsplitz expressly disclaims any warranties or representations (express or implied) in respect of Trips, accuracy, reliability and completeness of information provided by Members, or the content (including details of the Trip and Cost Contribution) on the Site. While Tripsplitz will take precautions to avoid inaccuracies in content of the Site, all content and information, are provided on an as is where is basis, without warranty of any kind. Tripsplitz does not implicitly or explicitly support or endorse any of the Members availing Services from the Site.

4.3 Tripsplitz is not a party to any agreement between a Trip Sharer and Trip Splitter and will not be liable to either the Trip Sharer or the Trip Splitter unless the loss or damage incurred arises due to Tripsplitz’s negligence.

4.4 Tripsplitz shall not be liable for any loss, damage or personal injury arising as a result of:

A false, misleading, inaccurate or incomplete information being provided by a Member;

The cancellation of a Trip by a Trip Sharer or Trip Splitter;

Any failure to make payment of a Cost Contribution (for the free service without booking);

Any fraud, fraudulent misrepresentation or breach of duty or breach of any of these Conditions by a Trip Sharer or Trip Splitter before, during or after a Trip.

Tripsplitz will not be liable to any Member for any business, financial or economic loss or for any consequential or indirect loss such as lost reputation, lost bargain, lost profit, lost of anticipated savings or lost opportunity arising as a result of the services provided by Tripsplitz (whether suffered or incurred as a result of the Tripsplitz’s negligence or otherwise) except in the case of fraud, wilful concealment or theft.

Tripsplitz’s liability to any Member for all losses in respect of any Trip is capped at the sum of GBP 100.00 (Great British Pounds One Hundred only).

Tripsplitz will not be liable to any Member in relation to any Trip unless Tripsplitz is notified of a claim relating to that Trip within 3 months of completion of the Trip

Given that Trip Sharers are required to ensure valid insurance to cover for a Trip and given that Tripsplitz’s service is limited to putting Trip Sharers and Trip Splitters in touch with each other and cannot oversee any Trip, Members accept that the limitations on the Tripsplitz’s liability set out above are reasonable.

5. INDEMNITY AND RELEASE

5.1 Members will indemnify and hold harmless Tripsplitz, its subsidiaries, affiliates and their respective officers, directors, agents and employees, from any claim or demand, or actions including reasonable attorney’s fees, made by any third party or penalty imposed due to or arising out of your breach of these Conditions or any document incorporated by reference, or your violation of any law, rules, regulations or the rights of a third party.

5.2 Members release Tripsplitz and/or its affiliates and/or any of its officers and representatives from any cost, damage, liability or other consequence of any of the actions/inactions of the Members and specifically waiver any claims or demands that they may have in this behalf under any statute, contract or otherwise.

6. LAW AND JURISDICTION

These terms shall be governed by the law of Great Britain and any disputes arising in relation to these terms shall be subject to the jurisdiction therein.
        "</string>
    <string name="download_tripsplit">Download Trip split app</string>
    <string name="logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="appdone">I have done what I need to do do</string>
    <string name="dontlike">"I didn't like the experience"</string>
    <string name="irrelevant">"Didn't find what I was looking for"</string>
</resources>
